Israel's Minister Of Tourism Yariv Levin Meets With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Welcome to Israel, welcome to Jerusalem - although I know it is almost a second home for you.
Thank you.
And of course, welcome to the Ministry of Tourism.
I must say I have read about your activities and first of all, I want to say, thank you.
I appreciate it very much -
seeing you as a prominent leader, saying things loud and clear and doing that on the ground.
Those who follow the truth in hard times, I believe that in the end, are remembered as real leaders.
We saw it in the past, in history and that's what will happen also regarding the times we live in.
I personally believe that for us in Israel, because we live here in the Holy Land,
making it possible for every believer, whether Jew, Christian or Muslim, to come here
to visit the holy places, to pray and do everything they want to do and feel safe while doing it,
is something that is not just an obligation but even a big right that we have
to make sure that all of that happens.
I do believe that making the possibility for people to come here and see things with their own eyes
and feel it, is much more than the ability to visit a place but rather an experience for life.
I believe that everyone who comes here goes back to their family and people as a different and better person.
In that aspect, I think that if we succeed in making it easier for more people to come here,
it’s not only a question of tourism but I believe it’s also a question of really giving people
something that is an added value for life and something that will fulfill our obligation.
Also, we are lucky to be in a place where we are able to do that.
In that aspect, I do believe in the potential of what we can do regarding tourism from Africa
as a whole and especially from Nigeria.
I believe that we are very far from exploiting the potential.
I believe we can do much more in order to do that.
We now have a much better cooperation with the Ministry of Interior regarding visas.
I'm really willing and at your disposal in order to hear what you expect from us.
Thank you.
Minister, I want to thank you for this great honour, for taking your time.
So, thank you very much.
I have been coming to Israel for many years; this is my home.
We have several travel agencies in Israel that are specialised in pilgrimage packages
that enable people to really visit the most important places and do it in a meaningful way.
I want to thank you, Minister, for your time and for your love.
We are at your disposal and we are really willing to help.
Thank you.
We see it as a really important initiative.
Please, don't hesitate to contact us to ask if there is anything you think that we can help with.
Thank you.
Just tell us.
Thank you very much.
Israel's Minister Of Tourism Yariv Levin Meets With Prophet T.B. Joshua
I'm Yariv Levin, Minister of Tourism for the state of Israel.
I just had a very important meeting with Prophet Joshua.
It was an honour for me to meet him.
So, the Holy Land is waiting for you.
Israel is waiting for you.
Please come here.
You are most welcome.
I'm Yariv Levin, Minister of Tourism for the state of Israel.
I call on you: Please, continue watching Emmanuel TV!
It's worth it.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Meets With The Chief Rabbi Of Israel, Rabbi David Lau In Jerusalem
It's a pleasure.
Thank you.
Chief Rabbi Of Israel, Rabbi David Lau Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua In Jerusalem
This is your home so we are brothers.
This is my home; I'm happy to meet you.
But I have the privilege that I was born here.
Chief Rabbi Of Israel, Rabbi David Lau Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua In Jerusalem
I'm happy that you are giving us your time.
You feel that this is your home.
You know, in the Bible you can find this sentence.
This is a person and person who was born in this place.
Our sages explain why the Bible says a person and person.
Why twice?
The explanation is, first a person who was born here and the second is to be spiritually born here.
Someone whose dream to feel at home here is exactly the same as someone who was born here.
What the Bible is trying to say there is someone who is born physically and spiritually.
There is also one who is born spiritually.
I am one of the children born spiritually but I was not born physically.
You were born physically and spiritually.
Because of that, I need your words because I know a lot of people who were born here but only physically.
They forgot about being born spiritually.
Because of that, your warm words help me to explain to people how important it is to be born here spiritually.
Thank you.
This is a very, very nice place.
It is my privilege to see you here and hear your words.
I want to tell you one more sentence.
This is a place where you can find all kinds of people.
I was in South Africa last year and they asked me about the differences between people -
if someone is a Muslim, Christian, Jew, black or white.
I told them they could see, in every hospital in Israel, in every department in Israel, you can see
among the people who treat and the people who need treatment,
you can see beds near each other and they help each other.
It doesn’t depend on whether you are a Jew or Muslim, Jew or Gentile.
Exactly.
Thank you.
What is unique about the hospitals in Israel
is that we take care of everybody and everybody takes care of everybody.
You can have nurses and doctors that are Arabs or Christians or Jews
and you can have people who are ill that are also Arabs, Christians or Jews.
That is the meaning of Holy Land.
Yes, this is the Holy Land.
The Holy Land accepts everyone.
Everyone wants to be holy.
In the Bible, you can find another sentence that says, all of us are children of God.
Because of that, I and you, he and she – all of us are children of one Father.
So, this is why I told you we are brothers.
Now, you can see it in the Bible.
Thank you.
Twenty-eight years ago, someone from Israel went to Nigeria to build telecommunications.
His flight was involved in an accident and all 143 people died.
The plane crashed.
His wife was in the city I was in as Chief Rabbi.
She called me and asked me what to do.
She didn’t know exactly if her husband had died or not.
She didn’t know whether she should mourn yet or not.
The details – she didn’t know.
I sent someone from Israel to your country.
He went there and found a taxi driver.
I have remembered the name for 28 years.
We spoke; he was the taxi driver that took him to the airport.
We spoke about it; I took all the details and told her I was sure that he had died.
Because of that, she could get married to another man.
It was something amazing; 28 years ago, communication was not as easy as today.
That is Nigeria, they love foreigners.
When they see that you are not a Nigerian but from another country, they are ready to die for you.
I felt it; it was such a warm help.
I am very thankful for it.
Chief Rabbi Of Israel, Rabbi David Lau Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua In Jerusalem
For me as a Chief Rabbi of Israel, it is a very great pleasure to meet you,
to see a lot of things you have done, giving all of your life and your power
and thinking about other people in the world - it is very nice to see it.
RV: Mel Flowers 23/03/2019